{
    "question": "Arrange these scramble letters to be correct words\r\na. o-h-u-m - t =\r\nb. e-S-O-n\r\nc. c-a-f-e\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. Mouth</p><p>B. Nose</p><p>C. Cafe</p><p></p><p>semoga membantu....?</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "dayu-the-schoolyard-is-very-large-a-say-b-says-c-saying-475",
            "question": "Dayu . . . the schoolyard is very large    A. say\r\n\r\nB. says\r\n\r\nC. saying\r\n\r\nD. is say\r\n\r\nmohon di bantu kak/bang\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>B. says</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>hope its right and helps!\u25c9\u203f\u25c9</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>jawaban: b.says</p><p>Dayu says the schoolyard is very large</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "what-is-the-message-can-be-found-in-the-text-above-668",
            "question": "What is the message can be found in the text above?\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>where&#039;s the text...?</p><p>U have to give the text..</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "terjemahkan-dengan-menggunakan-tenses-yang-tepat-a-andi-memberi-847",
            "question": "Terjemahkan dengan menggunakan tenses yang tepat    A. Andi memberi makan kucingnya 3 hari yang lalu sebelum kucingnya hilang\r\nB. Jill telah mengemudi selaman enam tahun\r\nC. Sam tidak menghadiri kelas matematika kemarin\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>J</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>w</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>b</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>n</strong><strong>:</strong></p><p><strong>A. Andi fed his cat 3 days ago before the cat disappeared</strong></p><p><strong>A. Andi fed his cat 3 days ago before the cat disappearedB. Jill has been driving for six years</strong></p><p><strong>A. Andi fed his cat 3 days ago before the cat disappearedB. Jill has been driving for six yearsC. Sam didn&#039;t attend math class yesterday</strong></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "i-always-pray-every-night-478",
            "question": "(+) I always pray every night\r\n (-)\r\n (?)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "I never pray every night<br>Am i pray every night?",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "(-) i never pray every night<br>(?) do i pray every night<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "complate-this-sentence-with-the-question-1-she-went-to-market-t-571",
            "question": "Complate this sentence with the question:    1. She went to market to sell her milk\r\n2. The farmer gave her a pail of milk.\r\n3. Molly warked for a farmer on his farm.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>2. The farmer gave her a pail of milk.</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf kalo salah</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "2-usually-a-wears-tigor-on-ascarf-windy-day-arrange-the-jumbled-666",
            "question": "2. Usually-a-wears-Tigor-on-ascarf-windy day Arrange the jumbled words to the correct sentences! A scarfusually wears Tigor on a windy day. b. Tigor usually wears a scarfon a windy day. On a windy day usually wear a Tigor scarf. d. Usually scarf Tigor wears on a windy day. C.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>b. Tigor usually wears a scarf on a windy day</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "jawablah-pertanyaan-berikut-deng-26-susan-do-you-like-red-skir-536",
            "question": "Jawablah pertanyaan berikut deng\r\n26. Susan : do you like red skirt?\r\nSonya : yes...\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Sonya:yes,i like red skirt</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "the-sulfur-oxides-and-nitrogen-oxides-will-in-the-air-121",
            "question": "The sulfur oxides and nitrogen oxides will ... in the air\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>The sulfur oxides and nitrogen oxides will <strong>evaporate</strong> in the air\u200b</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Sulfur oksida dan nitrogen oksida akan menguap di udara\u200b dan akan menimbulkan polusi udara, bahkan hujan asam yang sangat merugikan.</p><p>Semoga membantu ya.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "let-me-introduce-you-my-nam-ls-nurfaika-zamrah-im-16-years-616",
            "question": "Let me introduce you my nam ls nurfaika zamrah Im 16 years\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>hi there! nice to know you, have a great day!</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>greetings nurfaika</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>hi  </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "answer-by-using-comparative-or-superlative-degree-4-i-got-90-for-492",
            "question": "Answer by using comparative or superlative degree    4. I got 90 for English and I got 60 for Mathematic. For me, English is...\r\nthan Math\r\n5. Lina is 148 centimeters tall and Salsa is 145 centimeters tall. It means, lina is\r\nthan her older sister, Salsa\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>4. English is easier than math</p><p>5. It means,Lina is taller than her older sister,Salsa</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>uddaa yaa</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}